Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Box: 30, Folder: 145, Publication (Box 30, Folder 145)
  - Item 1: Tests, 1956; Publication (Box 30, Folder 145)
- Box: 30, Folder: 146, Publication (Box 30, Folder 146)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Chart, 1955; Publication (Box 30, Folder 146)
- Box: 30, Folder: 147, Publication (Box 30, Folder 147)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organizations Chart, 1956; Publication (Box 30, Folder 147)
- Box: 30, Folder: 148, Publication (Box 30, Folder 148)
  - Item 1: Suggested Minimum Test Scores, 1956; Publication (Box 30, Folder 148)
    Author: Howard C. Lockwood
- Box: 30, Folder: 149, Publication (Box 30, Folder 149)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Calendar, 1957; Publication (Box 30, Folder 149)
- Box: 30, Folder: 150, Publication (Box 30, Folder 150)
  - Item 1: Strikes and Lockouts, 1962; Publication (Box 30, Folder 150)
    Author: Courtlandt S. Gross &Daniel J. Haughton
- Box: 30, Folder: 151, Publication (Box 30, Folder 151)
  - Item 1: Orientation For Industrial Nurses, 1960; Publication (Box 30, Folder 151)
- Box: 30, Folder: 152, Publication (Box 30, Folder 152)
  - Item 1: Economics For Management, 1966; Publication (Box 30, Folder 152)
- Box: 30, Folder: 153, Publication (Box 30, Folder 153)
  - Item 1: Effective Employee Relations, 1966; Publication (Box 30, Folder 153)
- Box: 30, Folder: 154, Publication (Box 30, Folder 154)
  - Item 1: Missiles & Space Company, 1966; Publication (Box 30, Folder 154)
- Box: 30, Folder: 155, Publication (Box 30, Folder 155)
  - Item 1: Change of Status Notice, 1955; Publication (Box 30, Folder 155)
- Box: 30, Folder: 156, Publication (Box 30, Folder 156)
  - Item 1: Letter To Mr. J. Douglas Brown, 1955; Publication (Box 30, Folder 156)
- Box: 30, Folder: 157, Publication (Box 30, Folder 157)
  - Item 1: Checklist Of Material Needed On Company Industrial Relations Activities, 1954; Publication (Box 30, Folder 157)
- Box: 30, Folder: 158, Publication (Box 30, Folder 158)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Organization, 1953; Publication (Box 30, Folder 158)
- Box: 30, Folder: 159, Publication (Box 30, Folder 159)
  - Item 1: Rating, 1954; Publication (Box 30, Folder 159)
- Box: 30, Folder: 160, Publication (Box 30, Folder 160)
  - Item 1: Absentee and Quit Rates- First Quarter 1953, Publication (Box 30, Folder 160)
- Box: 30, Folder: 161, Publication (Box 30, Folder 161)
  - Item 1: Job Analysis, 1949; Publication (Box 30, Folder 161)
- Box: 30, Folder: 162, Publication (Box 30, Folder 162)
  - Item 1: Wage Chronology No. 23, 1954; Publication (Box 30, Folder 162)
- Box: 30, Folder: 163, Publication (Box 30, Folder 163)
  - Item 1: Wage Chronology No. 23, 1954; Publication (Box 30, Folder 163)
- Box: 30, Folder: 164, Publication (Box 30, Folder 164)
  - Item 1: Checklist Of Material Needed On Company Industrial Relations Activities, 1952; Publication (Box 30, Folder 164)
- Box: 30, Folder: 165, Publication (Box 30, Folder 165)
  - Item 1: Lockheed Strikes, 1952; Publication (Box 30, Folder 165)
- Box: 30, Folder: 166, Publication (Box 30, Folder 166)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Calendar, 1951; Publication (Box 30, Folder 166)
- Box: 30, Folder: 167, Publication (Box 30, Folder 167)
  - Item 1: Employee Application, Publication (Box 30, Folder 167)
- Box: 30, Folder: 168, Publication (Box 30, Folder 168)
  - Item 1: Employee Periodic Review, Publication (Box 30, Folder 168)
- Box: 30, Folder: 169, Publication (Box 30, Folder 169)
  - Item 1: Wage Chronology No. 23, 1960; Publication (Box 30, Folder 169)
- Box: 30, Folder: 170, Publication (Box 30, Folder 170)
  - Item 1: Technical and Office Jobs, 1959; Publication (Box 30, Folder 170)
- Box: 30, Folder: 171, Publication (Box 30, Folder 171)
  - Item 1: Management Evaluation, 1959; Publication (Box 30, Folder 171)
- Box: 30, Folder: 172, Publication (Box 30, Folder 172)
  - Item 1: Factory Jobs Index, 1959; Publication (Box 30, Folder 172)
- Box: 30, Folder: 173, Publication (Box 30, Folder 173)
  - Item 1: Factory Jobs Description, 1954; Publication (Box 30, Folder 173)
- Box: 30, Folder: 174, Publication (Box 30, Folder 174)
  - Item 1: Corporate Records Management Manual, 1964; Publication (Box 30, Folder 174)
- Box: 30, Folder: 175, Publication (Box 30, Folder 175)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1966; Publication (Box 30, Folder 175)
- Box: 30, Folder: 176, Publication (Box 30, Folder 176)
  - Item 1: Functions and Responsibilities: Director of Industrial Relations, 1966; Publication (Box 30, Folder 176)
- Box: 30, Folder: 177, Publication (Box 30, Folder 177)
  - Item 1: Evaluation Plan For Salaried Managerial Jobs, 1962; Publication (Box 30, Folder 177)
- Box: 30, Folder: 178, Publication (Box 30, Folder 178)
  - Item 1: Selection Of Salaried Personnel, 1963; Publication (Box 30, Folder 178)
- Box: 30, Folder: 179, Publication (Box 30, Folder 179)
  - Item 1: Evaluation Under SCAI Restudy Factory Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 30, Folder 179)
- Box: 30, Folder: 180, Publication (Box 30, Folder 180)
  - Item 1: Education and Training of Lockheed Personnel, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 180)
- Box: 31, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Lift Truck Operation Safety Rules, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Box: 31, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Lift Truck Operation Safety Rules, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Box: 31, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Gamma-Ray Operation Safety Rules, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Box: 31, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Paint Safety Operation Safety Rules, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Box: 31, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Personal Protective Equipment Safety Rules, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Box: 31, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Box: 31, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Crane Operation Safety Rules, 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Box: 31, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules For The Transportation Department, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Box: 31, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules For The Hooking Up Of Materials, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Box: 31, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Shearing and Scrap Cutting Operation Safety Rules, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Box: 31, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Loading Bank Safety Rules, 1948; Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Box: 31, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Grinding Operation Safety Rules, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Box: 31, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Paint Spray Operation Safety Rules, 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Box: 31, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Flanging Department Safety Rules, 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Box: 31, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Narrow Gauge Yard Switching and Boom Crane Operation Safety Rules, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Box: 31, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Crane Operation Safety Rules, 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Box: 31, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Systems, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Box: 31, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Payroll Deductives, 1963; Publication (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Box: 31, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Pension Benefits, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Box: 31, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Wage Rates, 1961; Publication (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Box: 31, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Program of Insurance Benefits, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Box: 31, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Program of Insurance Benefits, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Box: 31, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Box: 31, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Setting Corporate Objectives, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Box: 31, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Box: 31, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Box: 31, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Position of The Independent Company In Relation To The Overall Steel Industry, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: Charles Lukens Houston, Jr.
- Box: 31, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Box: 31, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Box: 31, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Flanging Department Safety Rules, 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Box: 31, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 31)
- Box: 31, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 32)
- Box: 31, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules For Gas Welding and Burning Operations, 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 33)
- Box: 31, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Systems, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 34)
- Box: 31, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Saving Plans & Vacations, 1966; Publication (Box 31, Folder 35)
- Box: 31, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 31, Folder 36)
- Box: 31, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Floor Operated Crane Safety Rules, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 37)
- Box: 31, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Color Identification of Pipe Lines, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 38)
- Box: 31, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 39)
- Box: 31, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Crane Operation Safety Rules, 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 40)
- Box: 31, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules For The Storage and Use of Paint, Solvents and Other Flammable Liquids, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 41)
- Box: 31, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules For Gas Welding and Burning Operations, 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 42)
- Box: 31, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Grinding Operation Safety Rules, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 43)
- Box: 31, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules For The Hook-Up of Materials, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 44)
- Box: 31, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Floor Operated Crane Safety Rules, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 45)
- Box: 31, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Open Hearth Safety Rules, 1959; Publication (Box 31, Folder 46)
- Box: 31, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules For The Operation of Materials Handling Vehicles, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 47)
- Box: 31, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Employee Retirement Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 31, Folder 48)
- Box: 31, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Vacations & Savings Plan, 1970; Publication (Box 31, Folder 49)
- Box: 31, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Profit Sharing, 1963; Publication (Box 31, Folder 50)
- Box: 31, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Payroll Deductions, 1963; Publication (Box 31, Folder 51)
- Box: 31, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules For Gamma Ray and X-Ray Operations, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 52)
- Box: 31, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Pension Benefits, 1969; Publication (Box 31, Folder 53)
- Box: 31, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Program of Insurance Benefits, 1970; Publication (Box 31, Folder 54)
- Box: 31, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Major Medical Expense Benefits, 1970; Publication (Box 31, Folder 55)
- Box: 31, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Savings and Vacation Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 31, Folder 56)
- Box: 31, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan For Hourly Rated Production and Maintenance Employees, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 57)
- Box: 31, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules For Inspection Department, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 58)
- Box: 31, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Regulations For The Use Of Ladders, 1957; Publication (Box 31, Folder 59)
- Box: 31, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: General Safety Rules, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 60)
- Box: 31, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Flanging Department Safety Rules, 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 61)
- Box: 31, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Eye Protection Regulations, 1959; Publication (Box 31, Folder 62)
- Box: 31, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 31, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Procedure For Use Of Red And Green Safety Tags, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 63)
- Box: 31, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 31, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Savings and Vacation Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 31, Folder 64)
- Box: 31, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 31, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Program of Insurance Benefits, 1970; Publication (Box 31, Folder 65)
- Box: 31, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 31, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, 1947; Publication (Box 31, Folder 66)
- Box: 31, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 31, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules For Sodium Hydride Descaling and Pickling, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 67)
- Box: 31, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 31, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules For The Operation of Presses, 1957; Publication (Box 31, Folder 68)
- Box: 31, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 31, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Crane Operation Safety Rules, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 69)
- Box: 31, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 31, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Always Be Careful, Publication (Box 31, Folder 70)
- Box: 31, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 31, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Supervisor Development, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 71)
- Box: 31, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 31, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: The Labor Management Center, 1965; Publication (Box 31, Folder 72)
- Box: 31, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 31, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Systems, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 73)
- Box: 31, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 31, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 74)
- Box: 31, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 31, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations System Chart, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 75)
- Box: 31, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 31, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 76)
- Box: 31, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 31, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Management Newsletter, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 77)
- Box: 31, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 31, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 78)
- Box: 31, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 31, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Training Outline, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 79)
- Box: 31, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 31, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 80)
- Box: 31, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 31, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 81)
- Box: 31, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 31, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Shearing and Scrap Cutting Operation Safety Rules, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 82)
- Box: 31, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 31, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Responsibilities of Supervision In Effecting Certain Phases of The Company Safety Program, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 83)
- Box: 31, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 31, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Responsibilities of Supervision In Effecting Good Housekeeping Throughout The Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 84)
- Box: 31, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 31, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Lafayette College Scholarship Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 31, Folder 85)
- Box: 31, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 31, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Clad & Alloy, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 86)
- Box: 31, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 31, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: By-Products Steel Company, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 87)
- Box: 31, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 31, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Pack Welding, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 88)
- Box: 31, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 31, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Machine, Forge, Roll, Carpenter & Pattern Shops, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 89)
- Box: 31, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 31, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Lukenweld, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 90)
- Box: 31, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 31, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Inspection Department, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 91)
- Box: 31, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 31, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Industrial Engineering, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 92)
- Box: 31, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 31, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Flanging Department, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 93)
- Box: 31, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 31, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Engineering Department, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 94)
- Box: 31, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 31, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Electrical Department, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 95)
- Box: 31, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 31, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Controllers Division, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 96)
- Box: 31, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 31, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: Production and Control Department, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 97)
- Box: 31, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 31, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Open Hearth Steel Making, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 98)
- Box: 31, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 31, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: Mechanical Department, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 99)
- Box: 31, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 31, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: Metallurgical Department, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 100)
- Box: 31, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 31, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: Refactories and Fuel, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 101)
- Box: 31, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 31, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: Foreman's Accident Report, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 102)
- Box: 31, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 31, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: Safety Contacts, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 103)
- Box: 31, Folder: 104, Publication (Box 31, Folder 104)
  - Item 1: Foreman's Safety Talks Report, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 104)
- Box: 31, Folder: 105, Publication (Box 31, Folder 105)
  - Item 1: Safety Committee Guide, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 105)
- Box: 31, Folder: 106, Publication (Box 31, Folder 106)
  - Item 1: General Safety Rules, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 106)
- Box: 31, Folder: 107, Publication (Box 31, Folder 107)
  - Item 1: Management Newsletter, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 107)
- Box: 31, Folder: 108, Publication (Box 31, Folder 108)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Systems, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 108)
- Box: 31, Folder: 109, Publication (Box 31, Folder 109)
  - Item 1: Employee Forms, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 109)
- Box: 31, Folder: 110, Publication (Box 31, Folder 110)
  - Item 1: Test of Particle Judgment, 1948; Publication (Box 31, Folder 110)
- Box: 31, Folder: 111, Publication (Box 31, Folder 111)
  - Item 1: Lukograph, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 111)
- Box: 31, Folder: 112, Publication (Box 31, Folder 112)
  - Item 1: Keystone Visual Test, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 112)
- Box: 31, Folder: 113, Publication (Box 31, Folder 113)
  - Item 1: Lukens Life, 1963; Publication (Box 31, Folder 113)
- Box: 31, Folder: 114, Publication (Box 31, Folder 114)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation/ Analysis, 1959; Publication (Box 31, Folder 114)
- Box: 31, Folder: 115, Publication (Box 31, Folder 115)
  - Item 1: Wage Rates, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 115)
- Box: 31, Folder: 116, Publication (Box 31, Folder 116)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Chart, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 116)
- Box: 31, Folder: 117, Publication (Box 31, Folder 117)
  - Item 1: Accidental Prevention, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 117)
- Box: 31, Folder: 118, Publication (Box 31, Folder 118)
  - Item 1: Rules For Dispensing Gasoline, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 118)
- Box: 31, Folder: 119, Publication (Box 31, Folder 119)
  - Item 1: Rules For Use of Compressed Gas Cylinders, 1957; Publication (Box 31, Folder 119)
- Box: 31, Folder: 120, Publication (Box 31, Folder 120)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 120)
- Box: 31, Folder: 121, Publication (Box 31, Folder 121)
  - Item 1: Head Protection Regulations, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 121)
- Box: 31, Folder: 122, Publication (Box 31, Folder 122)
  - Item 1: Layout of Employment Department, 1941; Publication (Box 31, Folder 122)
- Box: 31, Folder: 123, Publication (Box 31, Folder 123)
  - Item 1: Corporate Objectives, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 123)
- Box: 31, Folder: 124, Publication (Box 31, Folder 124)
  - Item 1: Base Salary Rate Schedule, 1957; Publication (Box 31, Folder 124)
- Box: 31, Folder: 125, Publication (Box 31, Folder 125)
  - Item 1: Savings Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 125)
- Box: 31, Folder: 126, Publication (Box 31, Folder 126)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 126)
- Box: 31, Folder: 127, Publication (Box 31, Folder 127)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 127)
- Box: 31, Folder: 128, Publication (Box 31, Folder 128)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 128)
- Box: 31, Folder: 129, Publication (Box 31, Folder 129)
  - Item 1: Specification of Training Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 31, Folder 129)
- Box: 31, Folder: 130, Publication (Box 31, Folder 130)
  - Item 1: Employee Educational Progress Report, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 130)
- Box: 31, Folder: 131, Publication (Box 31, Folder 131)
  - Item 1: Reading List, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 131)
- Box: 31, Folder: 132, Publication (Box 31, Folder 132)
  - Item 1: Tuition Refund Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 132)
- Box: 31, Folder: 133, Publication (Box 31, Folder 133)
  - Item 1: Functional Organization Chart, 1957; Publication (Box 31, Folder 133)
- Box: 31, Folder: 134, Publication (Box 31, Folder 134)
  - Item 1: Definitions of Measurement Factors For Position Evaluation, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 134)
- Box: 31, Folder: 135, Publication (Box 31, Folder 135)
  - Item 1: Position Description, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 135)
- Box: 31, Folder: 136, Publication (Box 31, Folder 136)
  - Item 1: By-Products Steel Company Lukenweld, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 136)
- Box: 31, Folder: 137, Publication (Box 31, Folder 137)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Chart, 1957; Publication (Box 31, Folder 137)
- Box: 31, Folder: 138, Publication (Box 31, Folder 138)